Carla: What’s the matter?
Emma: Ben has another one of Izzy’s work events tonight.
Carla: And that’s a bad thing?
Ben: This is what it’s like:
Nice to meet you, Ben.
You work in a café?
Aw, you’re so lucky.
I love coffee.
People always need coffee.
Neh, neh, neh, neh, neh.
Ha ha ha.
Carla: Really?
Are they all like that?
Emma: But that’s not the real problem, is it Ben?
Ben: No, it isn’t.
It’s Izzy.
She’s different when she’s with the people from work.
Carla: Well, she’s working.
We’re all different at work, aren’t we?
Hi, can I help you?
To have here or take away?
Thanks very much.
Have a nice day!
Emma: Well, I’m not different at work.
Carla: You work on a farm!
You spend most of your time talking to animals!
Ben: I know it’s because she’s at work,
but…she’s always at work.
I don’t want to spend all our free time with her work friends, especially Max.
Carla: Well, I’m sure you’re going somewhere really nice this evening.
Ben: ‘This evening’
I would just like to have a pizza with my girlfriend on the sofa in her apartment.
I don’t want to have to dress up and go out to a nice restaurant.
I want it to be like before.
I want Izzy back!
Carla: Izzy is still here.
Emma: Is she…?
Ben: I don’t know.